Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/malvika-shah-462494184 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Core Java

С

Languages

Gujarati (Full Professional) Spanish (Elementary) Hindi (Full Professional)

Certifications

International Software Testing Qualifications Board

MALVIKA SHAH

Data Scientist at Amazon

Irvine, California

Summary

Experienced Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Requirements Analysis, Servlets, Databases, PL/SQL, and Eclipse. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Engineering from Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay.

Experience

Amazon

Data Scientist

February 2017 - Present (3 years 2 months)

Irvine, California Area

Tata Consultancy Services Software Engineer August 2010 - December 2016 (6 years 5 months) Mumbai Area, India

Worked on a web application based on Struts framework for Siemens Employees used for Invoice approval and processing.

The web application focused on the concepts of JSP, Javascript, CSS, Jquery and AJAX for front end and SQL database for backend.

Provided end to end solution for the new change requests for SAP Integration with web based application.

Involvement in requirement gathering and Impact Analysis phase for the new projects and make sure all that all the phases of Software development life cycle are properly followed.

Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay
Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering (2006 - 2010)